Guide to the Robert L. Bracklow Photograph Collection 1882-1918 (bulk, 1896-1905) PR 8
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Trappan Gift: Photograph Albums, 2
  - Subseries II.2: "Glimpses Through the Camera" [Album 1], 2
    - Road to "the Wayside Inn" [Sudbury (Mass.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
      Same image as Alland # 2182
    - The Hollow Oak [Sudbury (Mass.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - The Latest WAR SHOW, near Iron Pier [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Street in India [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - West Brighton Beach [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Fort Hamilton [Fort Hamilton (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - En route to 39th Street, South Brooklyn [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - New York Harbor [Fort Hamilton (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Fort Hamilton [Fort Hamilton (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - U.S. Naval Boats [New York (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - U.S. Naval Boats [New York (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Coney Island, old Iron Pier [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Copy of a lithographic print - 5th Avenue, bet. 37 & 38th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - A Happy party - out for a ride [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Sky study - clouds [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Sea Scape [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - An offshore view [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Moonlight on the Bay [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Bay and bathers [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Bay and bathers [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Survey of the Manor of Queens Village 1722 [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Oyster Bay and the Neck from the beach [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Lloyd's Harbor from the Beach road [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Fort Hill Point, etc. from the wharf [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Harbor Road [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Oyster Bay from the Fort Hill House [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Fort Hill House, from the East [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Within the Ramparts - "1781" - Fort Hill House [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Vista, looking west, Oyster Bay and lighthouse [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Vista, looking southeast from Fort Hill [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - The Dower House, Fort Hill [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Over the cornfield, distant view of the houses on Fort Hill [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - The Cottage Lot, from the beach [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Fresh Water Pond [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Large Tree and Field [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Mr. Schmidt's House, on the harbor side [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - First Manor House, built in 1711 [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Barns and Farmhouse [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - The Manor House, from the southeast [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - The Manor House, from the southwest [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Looking off to the southwest from the Manor House [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Sheds and Outhouses [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Trees and Field [Lloyd Harbor (N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Memorial Bridge, 1639-1889 [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Memorial Bridge & Stream [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Bridge, Tower and street [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Stream below the bridge [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Memorial Tower and bridge [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Taylor Library [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church-Taylor Memorial [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - The Green [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - The Park Hotel [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Town Hall [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Water Works. Site of Dam I, looking west [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Water Works. Site of Dam II, looking west [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Water Works. Site of Dam III, looking east [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Water Works. Pond and site for reservoir [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Water Works. Sod-hut of Italian Laborers [Milford (Conn.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - The pleasures of Portraying a Group I [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - The pleasures of Portraying a Group II [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Our Euchre Club. The pleasures of Portraying a Group III [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Heiterkeit, II [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
    - Achtung! IV [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Offsite-box 20, Box 20, Album 1)
  - Subseries II.3: "Vacation" [Album 2], 3
    - Market Square [Newburyport (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
      Same image as Alland # 965
    - Cathedral of the Incarnation [Garden City (N.Y.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
      Same image as Alland # 1734A
    - St. Luke's Hospital [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
      Same image as Alland # 1261
    - Metropolitan Opera House [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
      Same image as Alland # 1236
    - N.Y. Herald Building - from Broadway just north of 36th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
      Same image as Alland # 1094A
    - N.Y. Herald Building - from Broadway, just north of 34th street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
      Same image as Alland # 1094
    - Statue of Horace Greeley - Greeley Square [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
      Same image as Alland # 1200
    - John Dempsey's hansom - Greeley Square [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
      Same image as Alland # 1473
    - U.S.S. Columbia [Hudson River (N.Y.and N.J.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
      Same image as Alland # 1324
    - U.S.S. Indiana [Hudson River (N.Y.and N.J.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
      Same image as Alland # 1324A
    - Church Street and School Street [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Monument of Commodore Matthew C. Perry-Touro Park [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Old Mill or tower-Touro Park [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Monument of Rev. William E. Channing - Touro Park [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - View of the harbor [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - The harbor, Goat Island in the distance. Taken from the foot of Mill St. [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Monument of Com. Oliver Perry, Washington Square [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - View of Washington Square and monument of Com. Oliver Perry, from a window of the Perry House [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - State House, built in 171, north end and front [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - State House, south end and rear [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Presbyterian Church, Broadway [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Soldiers & Sailors Monument [Newport (R.I.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Some old time houses, Centre Street [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Old Warehouses on Front Street from the corner of Centre St. [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Custom House and Post Office, Williams Street [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Mariner's Home and the Seaman's Bethel, Bethel Street [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Old Whaling Ships, Centre Street Wharf [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Old Whaling Ships [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Wharf and the ship "Bertha," Bridge and Fish Island in the distance [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - A Fish Market [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Wharfs and river, from the bridge between the city and Fish Island [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - A glimpse of city from Fish Island [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Wharfs from Fish Island [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Schooners: Pedro Varela and C. W. Morse, Fish Island and church spires of the city in the background [New Bedford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - A bit of Bridge Street, near the river [Fairhaven (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Millicent Library [Fairhaven (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Residence of Mr. Henry H. Rogers, near Fort Phoenix [Fairhaven (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - View of the harbor, steamboat, wharf [Provincetown (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - A glimpse of town, from the steamboat wharf [Provincetown (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Town Hall, with "Mayflower" compact stone [Provincetown (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Commercial Street, toward the outskirts of town [Provincetown (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Glimpse of the harbor, from the Gifford House, observatory "piazza" [Provincetown (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Rear view of Gifford House [Provincetown (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Odd Fellows Hall [Provincetown (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Alden Street, and school house [Provincetown (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - State House [Boston (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Statue of Christopher Columbus, Louisburg Square [Boston (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Louisburg Square (statue of Aristedes) from Chestnut Street [Boston (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Soldiers and Sailor Monument - Flagstaff Hill Common [Boston (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - City Hall [Cambridge (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Cradock House, built in 1634 [Medford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Garrison House, built by Jonathan Wade, before 1689 [Medford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Medford Savings Bank [Medford (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Hotel Whittier [Hampton (N.H.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Toppan House, built in 1720 [Hampton (N.H.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Moulton House, built shortly after 1769 [Hampton (N.H.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - John J. Mace's cottage, at "the bridge on the old causeway" [Hampton Falls (N.H.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Elmfield [Hampton Falls (N.H.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Large elm near the "Elmfield" house [Hampton Falls (N.H.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Monument of Gov. Weare, the first governor of New Hampshire [Hampton Falls (N.H.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Apple tree and little brown house, near the station [Hampton Falls (N.H.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Custom House [Newburyport (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Bridge over Parker River [Newbury (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Parker River, looking outward [Newbury (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - 1775 Monument [Newbury (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Coffin House, built 1645 [Newbury (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Coffin House, built 1645 [Newbury (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Jesse Gearing, and his team [Newburyport (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Washington statue, High Street Mall [Newburyport (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - The Athenaeum [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - First Church and City Hall [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - St. Stephen's Church [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - East Street, looking north-east [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - East Street, looking westward [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Appleton House, "the old clock on the stairs" [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Street Scene [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - A family group [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - The library corner [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Antiques-Plum Street [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - American House, on North Street [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Pontoosuc Lake, "Point of Pines" at left [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Point of Pines, Pontoosuc Lake [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - Lake Onota [Pittsfield (Mass.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
    - U.S.S. New York [Hudson River (N.Y.and N.J.)], 1896 (Offsite-box 21, Box 21, Album 2)
  - Subseries II.4: "Three Outings" [Album 3], 4
    - Washington's Headquarters (Ford House), view from the north-east [Morristown (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
      Same image as Alland # 22
    - Old Jones House [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - The rectory of St. Andrew's Protestant Episcopal Church [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Gen. Howe's Headquarters [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - St. Andrew's P.E. Church [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - House on Fresh Kills Road [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Row of willow trees on the Fresh Kills road [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Brook & bridge [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Dogwood tree in full bloom [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Trees, brook, & reflections [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - The pilgrims, at rest [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Ford House from the south-east [Morristown (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Old fashioned divided doorway in the Ford House [Morristown (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - The Morris house, corner of Spring and Water Streets [Morristown (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - A bit of Morristown, from a Spring St. vacant lot [Morristown (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Park Place from South Street [Morristown (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Park Place from South Street [Morristown (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Park Square from South Street [Morristown (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Falls on the Rockaway River [Boonton (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Falls on the Rockaway River [Boonton (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Stone Bridge near the Rockaway River [Boonton (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Two little maids from school, reading in shade of trees [New Jersey], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Two pair and a "Brownie" in the woods [New Jersey], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
    - Morris Canal and the Rockaway River [Morris Canal (N.J.)], 1909 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 3)
      Note on print "From skyscraper competition, 1907. Negative and print by Wm. E. Wilmerding"
  - Subseries II.5: "New York" [Album 4], 5
    - Old house, S.W. corner Hudson & Charles Sts. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 1292
    - The face at the window [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 121
    - Fuller Building on the "Flat Iron" from Fifth Avenue, south of 20th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 1085
    - Ye Olde Taverne, 161 Duane St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 115A
    - Brown-stone house of "Engine Co. 7," Centre & Chambers Sts. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 115
    - Hall of Records-old-City Hall Park from the northeast-Centre Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 1092
    - Hall of Records-old-City Hall Park from the southwest [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 1259
    - Astor House, built 1834-6, B'way & Fulton Sts. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 1275
    - St. Paul, Park Bank, & Knox Buildings, Broadway down to Fulton [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 1207A
    - Boreel and Trinity buildings and Trinity Church from in front of 130 Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 1207
    - Trinity building from Pine Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
      Same image as Alland # 1275A
    - Trinity building from in front of 98 Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Broadway, looking south from in front of no. 166, near Maiden Lane [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - M. Ward's House, 23 Bond St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Lower front of the house of M. Ward, 23 Bond St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - An old fashioned extension, rear of 51 Bleecker St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Houses of Tom's father in law [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Houses of Tom's father in law [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Houses of Tom's father in law [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Academy of the Sacred Heart, 51-55 W. 17th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Yellow house, Kingsbridge Road and Valentine Avenue [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - St. James Church, Jerome Ave. & 190th St. [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Poe Cottage, Kingsbridge Road [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Poe Cottage, Kingsbridge Road [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Ye olde housen - south west corner broadway & Duane St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
    - Old Brownstone courthouse, City Hall Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 4)
  - Subseries II.6: "Dewey Days" [Album 5], 6
    - U.S.S. New York [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - U.S.S. Indiana [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - U.S.S. Chicago [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - How some of our neighbors saw the Naval Parade [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - How some other neighbors saw the Naval Parade [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Torpedo Boats and small craft [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Looking southeast, showing other neighbors watching Naval Parade [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch - Northwest corner of Fifth Avenue and 26 Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch - Fifth Avenue, looking south from southeast corner of 26th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch Group: Protection to Homes and Industries [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch Group: The Philippines [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch Group: Peace, by Daniel C. French [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Colonnade and Arch from Fifth Avenue and 22nd Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch from Broadway and 22 Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Fifth Ave. Hotel and Dewey Arch [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch Group: The Navy [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch Group: The Triumphant Return [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch Group: The Attack [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - East Side of Dewey Arch [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)